holidaytaxis.com 2006-11-02

# Holiday Taxis | Airport Transfers | Airport Taxi | Minibus | Limousines

|  |  |  |  |  |   
---  
NEWS...  
> Holiday Taxis News  
> Customer Testimonials  
> Shuttle Airport Transfers  
|  |  |   
---|---|---  
  
Home | How to Book | Destinations | FAQ | Contact Us | Guides | UK Partners | Jobs | UK transfers  
  
|   
|  |  |    
---  

| Quickquote  
---  
Select a destination  
Select an airport  
Select a resort  
Date of travel  
Note:  Please enter the exact date of arrival to ensure that you are quoted the correct rate as different seasons operate different prices.  
---  
|   
---  
|  | Privacy Policy  
---  
Holiday Taxis is the trading name of Airport to Hotel (UK) Limited whose registered number is 4391036 and whose registered address is - 1st Floor, Martlet Heights, 49 The Martlets, Burgess Hill, West Sussex, RH15 9NN. At Holiday Taxis we are committed to protecting your privacy and take the responsibility regarding the security of our customers' information very seriously. Please read the following for further details on our privacy policy.   
What information do we collect and how do we use it?  
In order to process your booking we do require certain information. This will include the name of the person making the booking, address, telephone number, email address, and your credit card number and expiry date. We also need to establish your flight details, destination resort and accommodation. All of this information is collated for different reasons. Obviously we need to establish your holiday details to ensure your taxi is waiting for the correct flight and knows which hotel to take you to. Your telephone/Email address are required in to send your booking confirmation and contact you in the unlikely event of any changes prior to departure. We need your address to assist in processing your credit card transaction as proof of authentication helping prevent any potential fraudulent activity.  
NB  
Credit card details will be handled securely to ensure confidentiality. SSL (Secure sockets layer) encryption is employed to ensure sensitive data is protected.  
Who do you share your information with?  
Holiday Taxis collates your information solely for the purpose of making your booking and does not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information with anyone.   
Holiday Taxis special offer service.  
[ Holiday Taxis have many trade partners who from time to time give us access to offers and promotions they may have running, allowing you to become one of the first to be notified of any great travel bargains. You give us prior authorisation to email these offers by registering on the website and can of course opt out by unsubscribing at any time.]   
Other Web sites  
There are several places on the Holiday Taxis Web site where you can link through to other sites. Once you click through onto another site, Holiday Taxis privacy practices no longer apply. We recommend you view privacy statements for all third party Web sites to understand their own policies for collecting and disclosing your information.  
Security and Data Protection  
In addition and as required by the UK Data Protection Legislation, (Acts of 1984 and 1998) we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us, to prevent unauthorised access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you.  
Cookies  
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computers hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Cookies can be deleted from your hard drive if you wish. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser settings to prevent that. Even without a cookie you can still use most of the features on the web site.  
Your Consent  
By using the Holiday Taxis Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Holiday Taxis in the ways outlined above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of the information that we collect, how we use it and in what circumstances we disclose it.  
|  |   
---|---|---  
Sitemap | Press Articles | About Us | Privacy Policy | Terms & Conditions | [Majorca Transfers](http://www.majorcataxis.com/)  

#### [Copyright © 2006 Holiday Taxis, Airport Taxi, Minibus & Shuttle Transfers ](http://www.holidaytaxis.com/)
